NGUYEN QUANG THANH NAM

Thu Duc district, Ho Chi Minh city

 \boxtimes

CAREER GOALS

A committed individual with creativity and advanced problem-solving skills looking to bring value to a position of quality to increase efficiency within manufacturing. I am searching for work in a professional and challenging working environment. Becoming a manager or head of the department is the objective for the following three to five years.

EDUCATION

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology (HCMUT)

08/2018 - 11/2022

Major: Biotechnology

Grade: Good

WORK EXPERIENCE

Thagri Feed Long An Limited Liability Company - THACO AGRI

09/2023 - Present

QA/QC staff

Inspect samples of raw materials, semi-products, and finished products in the process according to standards

Develop and draft standards, processes, and documents on quality management systems

Collect and analyze data and results to optimize processes

Operate NIR equipment, be in charge of planning and sending samples for analysis

The Laboratory of Magnetic Nanomaterials, Institute of Physics

02/2019 - 04/2023

Vietnam Academy of Science And Technology (VAST)

Researcher

Research and develop a process for synthesizing nanomaterials

Synthesis of precious metal nanomaterials (gold, silver, copper)

Collect data, write reports, manage laboratory

The Laboratory of Biotechnology, Faculty of Chemical Engineering

01/2022 - 10/2022

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology (HCMUT)

Researcher

Research the effect of silver nanoparticles on the growth and development of seedlings in vitro

Research and development of microponic systems

Navitek Products and Environmental Testing Joint Stock Company

10/2021 - 01/2022

Intern leader

Laboratory operation according to ISO 17025:2017

Carry out microbiological testing according to VILAS 1399 standard

CERTIFICATION

ACHIEVEMENTS

Quality management (Alison)

- ISO 9001:2015
- ISO 22000:2018
- FSSC 22000

Biosafety Awareness Training Course (Esco VietNam)

Occupational safety and health (THACO)

Co-author of 05 scientific articles (2 international, 3 domestic) Scholarship encouraging study

Consolation prize in Technology Festival - HCMUT (Leader)

Consolation prize in Chemical Storm Competion

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Teamwork	Presentation	Quality Management
Communication	Innovation	Office software
Data analysis	Problem solving	Labortatory skill

Languages

TOEIC: 665